And the source batch ID in the job
metadata table to get the the like source
job ID.
If we have multiple tables we have to do
this for every table.
After that the all these are are metadata
entries like for our target table job
metadata, job metadata,
ETL ingestion data metadata.
OK so I have only one source table for
this particular table so I made only one
entry and I have three DP checks so I
made three entries here.
So for the first time incremental as the
logic for this is not there.
And also here I we are making dummy
entries for source batch ID and source
job ID also why?
Because the entries are not in proper
condition to use like whatever the
entries that are made by zone one team
are not in a proper condition to test our
like data flowers.
OK so that is the reason why we are
making entries first for source.
So this is my source.
So I made entries into this table just I
have given instance ID as you want to
dummy.
OK,
let me show you the excel also parallel.
So here first we are making entry into
the batch table.
Batch run stable for source OK in John 1.
So in John 2 during the batch preload
process we are making one entry and
during batch post load we are updating
the same entry which is made in the
preload.
Whereas in John 1 they're making new
entry in the preload and also they are
making entry in in the post load as well.
So with the same execution run ID and
instance ID OK, OK.
That is the reason why per batch run they
will be having two entries.
So I'm just trying to make 2 entries.
The first two entries are there right?
So execution run ID first once you make
the entry into the table.
So whatever the execution run ID that you
got like you have to use the same in the
second run here I think.
So this execution run ID whatever the
alphanumeric value,
are you trying to curate it somewhere how
creating it somewhere or it is just a
random value.
So here I'm using this insert script
which will generate.
So first you we have to make this entry
whatever generated using the first line.
Once we make this entry,
let me copy it here.
So using this I'm making the first one is
GSU already Sorry batch ID,
Batch run ID is a hard coded value.
It's AU UUID field.
So we are using RRS RR postgres sequels
function random UID to generate that and
execution run ID is also her UUID and
instance ID.
I'm giving hard coded value as June to
dummy and batch end time,
batch start time, batch end Ms.
null status has started and source ID I
don't know that's why you have given null
and audit fails.
OK batch region flag is N so this is how
we have to make the first entry.
Once we make the first entry,
you can query the table then you will
find the execution run ID.
So for the first entry and like when you
make that entry in a table,
you'll get a execution run ID right?
So whatever the first execution run ID
that you got,
use the same execution run ID to make the
second entry.
Understood.
So use it same and while making the
second entry start time would be null but
end time would be some value and status
would be completed.
Like this you have to do for first time
incremental.
So first two entries are related to the
first time incremental and then for each
table we OK I'll tell you only about
first time incremental first.
So here I'm trying to do entry for source
table with job ID hundred 318.
This is the job ID so far.
This whatever the execution run ID that
we have used that we got while we are
making entry into the batch table,
that execution run ID,
we have to use it here, OK.
And job instance ID,
I'm taking the dummy entry just like in
batch run stats, John,
one team are making two entries per job
ID in preload and also in post load
they're making to and risk per job ID.
So zone one team like zone 1 table will
have multiple job IDs.
But we're focus like we're focusing or
we're considering only one job IDs status
and job end time to proceed with our zone
2 table table load.
OK,
so we mock the data only to that
particular job ID.
I'll tell you which job ID we have to
take.
So here while you are taking like here,
while I'm taking the job ID,
I'll be considering the entry with job
name raw to current data movement.
So this is the step where actual data
from source system to zone 1 table or
whatever the iceberg table we have that
is happening only in this table of their
job IDs.
They'll have multiple job IDs unlike us.
So out of this we are considering this
step.
If this is completed then we are good to
do our zone to load.
So we are mocking up data only for this
job IDs.
OK, are you following?
Yes, yes, please continue.
Yeah.
OK,
So that job idea I I have taken and in
the first entry I'll be taking only the
job start time.
In the second entry,
I I'm taking the job end time status
started,
completed and reminding all null and
dummy data that I have taken and audit
fields.
That's it.
OK I so this is related.
So here job run IDs would be different,
execution run IDs should be same and
instance ID should be same.
Job ID should also be same.
OK this is though this is how you have to
make dummy entries for first time
incremental in source for source tables
OK then coming to target.
So for target tables also you have to
make dummy entries in batch run stats job
understand ATL,
ATL data edition source window.
OK the source entries why we are making
because the entries like entries made by
the zone 1 table loads is not proper.
That is the reason why we are making it
this we are making it this we are making
as the logic for implementing first time
incremental in our table is not there.
That is the reason why we are making
target.
So here how we how we are making the
target.
So first one so use the first one.
OK we have only one singletry per passion.
So you can directly use the same query or
same line same query to do your batch
entry.
Just change batch ID and execution run ID
can also be UUID value only.
OK I don't know why I have changed
because multiple times I think people are
changing this.
That is the reason why I think this has
been updated.
You can directly use general random UUID
to generate execution run ID for the
first time.
OK posted it in the job run stats table
we can use.
We have to use the same execution run ID
which is used in our batch run stats to
make entry for our table load.
So this is the job ID, job start time,
job end time status completed and ran
like you can give some dummy values to
all the other fields.
OK and ATL sourcing ATL rendition source
window here.
If you have only one source table,
then make only one entry.
So whatever the execution run ID that is
inserted during the batch run stats entry,
use that and batch ID,
target job ID and target job ID.
So whenever you are making this first
entry to dummy entry,
use that job run ID here.
OK, and then table name,
source table name.
So source job run ID.
So while you're making source job entry,
so here you have to consider the job run
ID whose status is started, OK,
that job run ID you have to populate it
here, OK.
And then status is completed and you can,
we are considering both sourcing startup
and end time as 19119 hundred.
So whatever the run we are taking,
it will take whole data from the source.
For that reason we are taking both as
same value and audit fields.
OK so this is the these are the entries
that we are making for first time
incrementals for the current run.
Whatever the trigger that you are trying
to do from IDMC task flow for that run.
Also there should be entries for source.
These has to be ideally like if you if
you are so source two on one tables have
valid entries then you don't need to do
for source.
You can directly use them latest entry
you can consider it for the current run
and the entry which is made just before
that latest entry you can consider it as
a first time incremental.
Like that you can consider and you can do
it here all the tables are are having
foreign key constraint.
So that is the reason why if we may if we
don't make any entry it it won't allow
any dumb,
it won't allow any dummy value in foreign
key columns.
That is the reason why we are following
each and everything OK And for the
current run also we have to use a similar
similar approach to make dummy entries
first source match and source a target
batch OK.
So whatever this entry 3rd entry we have
user for making dummy entry into our
batch transcripts for source batch ID.
Similar way once you do this third entry
you will get execution run ID right Using
that execution run ID do the 4th entry
first source job this third entry
whatever the.
So I think here it is 15.
I have I think we have directly updated
in the Aurora not clear just OK.
So here we you can make all these entries
at once,
these two entries at once using this OK.
After that,
if you're directly triggering from the
batch task flow, then you're good,
you're good.
Like if you do these 76 and five entries
then you would be good to start your load.
If you are doing your testing from the
job level task flow,
then you have to make a dummy entry into
batch run stats also for your current
batch.
Because if you are running from the job
run stats table here will batch batch
runstarts preload component won't be
executed right?
For that reason whatever the entry that
has to be loaded that has to be loaded
into this batch runstart as part of batch
preload should be loaded manually by S OK
like this with starter status so that
every time it will be using these.
So in the in IDMC also we have to assign
all the input fields.
So this is our job level task flow.
We are doing as earlier multiple teams or
like multiple people are using doing the
loads and performing the UT right.
So we are we plan,
we have planned to use like run,
do unit testing from a job level task
flow.
So whatever the input fields that are
required which which are ideally should
be populated from the batch task flow.
But as we are running it from here,
so all the necessary initial value should
be kept here.
OK.
Then if you trigger this task loop,
then you you like whatever the like,
whatever the tab is that we have in
Snowflake will be automatically executed
and you will be having the sourcing
statum and sourcing anten to pull the
load to pull the records into your tab.
Yeah, good.
Yeah.
Can you share the tables which are,
which are to be populated manually and
also that sheet which you are editing,
this sheet is already shared Ray event,
this right is that same sheet, right.
I showed you the CCM entries.
Yes, it is different.
This is runtime entries.
But like, OK,
I'll be like I'm sharing to you by three
MLM, OK.
Yeah, Yeah.
Like don't make entries here.
You can take a copy of it and click it.
Yeah, sure.
Yeah.
So all the tables which are to be
populated or listed in that sheet rate.
Yeah,
but you have to understand why we are
loading it for each table.
So single like source,
it needs to be populated twice,
one for first time incremental,
one for current run.
You can just go through this recording
once again.
If you don't understand it,
you can follow it.
You will, you will get it.
If you have any questions,
you can bring in the group.
Sure.
Thank you.
I'm sharing shortly the downloader
version guys.
Yeah, thank you.
We have recordings across for all every
activity.
So go through the recordings if the
recordings doesn't provide you the
required information, right,
please do ping.
Sure.
Thanks a lot.
I shared that with AP because I already
started a chat and sent you a metadata
interest related XLS well.
So sharing here.
OK, You can call.
There's nothing any doubts.
If no doubts, we can close this call.
Thanks.
Yeah.
Thanks for the quick, quick, quick call.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Thank you, guys.
Thank you.
Thank you.